<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes | 星海小筑</title>
    <link>/home/</link>
      <atom:link href="/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Homes</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Homes</title>
      <link>/home/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>QCD@Energy Frontier Collaboration</title>
      <link>/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/home/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QCD@Energy Frontier</title>
      <link>/home/qcdef/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/home/qcdef/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;2020&#34;&gt;2020&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;august-21-friday-1pm----3pm&#34;&gt;August 21, Friday, 1pm &amp;ndash; 3pm.&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Forest-based Infrared Subtraction for Wide-angle Scattering&lt;/strong&gt;, Yao Ma, Stony Brook University
&lt;details&gt; &lt;summary&gt;Abstract (click to expand)&lt;/summary&gt;
I will develop a BPHZ-like forest formula to subtract the IR singularities systematically in QCD. A related analysis has been carried out by Collins for the back-to-back Sudakov form factors, and is generalized here to any wide-angle kinematics with an arbitrary number of external momenta. After a brief introduction to Minkowskian IR divergences in momentum space, I will first illustrate that the approximations yield much richer IR structures than those of an original amplitude, then construct the forest formula and prove that all the singularities appearing in its subtraction terms cancel pairwise. Finally, with the help of this forest formula, the full amplitude can be reorganized into a factorized expression, proving the all-order hard-soft-collinear factorization.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Calculation of Multi-loop Feynman Integrals&lt;/strong&gt;, Long-Bin Chen, Guangzhou University
&lt;details&gt; &lt;summary&gt;Abstract (click to expand)&lt;/summary&gt;
Feynman integrals are essential for multi-loop calculations. Understanding the mathematical structure of Feynman integrals will be important to handle the complexity of their calculation and may help us to obtain a better understanding of the perturbative quantum field theory. The study of the mathematical properties of Feynman integrals has attracted increasing attention both by the physics and the mathematics communities. Significant progresses were achieved in understanding the analytical computations of multi-loop Feynman integrals in recent years. In this talk, I will present some of our recent works on the analytic calculations of Feynman integrals, which are based on the method of differential equations along with the choice of canonical basis.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
